NGUYEN MAI CHI TRUNG | FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Ho Chi Minh City | 0357640009 | nguyenmaichitrung1912@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/trungnguyen1912/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a Front-End Developer with 3 years of web development experience. I have a high level of proficiency in HTML, CSS and JavaScript, along with famous libraries and frameworks like ReactJS, NextJS,... My strengths are logical thinking and solving complex problems. I want to build a practical, extensible, maintainable, and highly available system.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022 | University of Transport and Communications

Major: Information technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

FPT Software

Web Developer | Dec 2021 - Present

- Implement web design and development principles to build stable software using ReactJS, VueJS, NextJS, HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, Jquery, and TypeScript.
- Collaborate closely with the team to support projects during all phases of delivery.
- Analyze requirements, investigate issues, and propose solutions.
- Test and perform quality assurance of various cross-platform software products.

Mevivu

Intern Web Developer | Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

- Implement web design and development principles to build stable software using HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, Jquery and ReactJS.
- Collaborate closely with the team to update the website and create new features.
- Successfully completed and handed over many projects to customers.

RELEVANT PROJECTS

ASCOTT BRAND (https://www.discoverasr.com/en)

- The project entailed the creation of a branded website that allows end users to book apartments using specific vouchers and promotional codes. It incorporates complex logic in the background to calculate prices based on different coupon types, promo codes, and membership levels.
- Team size: 40
- I was responsible for create new screen UI, new components, fix bug and implement task. Set up project's environment
- Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, VueJS, Figma, Git, Azure, Jira,...

JOB KOREA (https://www.albamon.com/)

- Professional part-time job search site created by Job Korea. Albamon offers web and app versions, target customers are both job seekers and companies. Users can search for part time job information by working location, working time, industry field, wage, bonus,....
- Team size: over 50
- As a Frontend Developer, I analyzed requirements, investigated issues, and proposed solutions. Additionally, I created reusable components that can be used multiple times that reduces the coding time and followed the procedure to deliver a good product for the customer.
- Technology: HTML, CSS, TypeScript, NextJS, Figma, Git, Chart.js, GSAP, Azure, Jira,...

CLS_GTO

- Revamp existing portal for CLs retails POS integration
- Team size: over 140
- In the project, I participated as a Front-end Developer, where my responsibilities included creating the user interface (UI), fixing bugs and comments, refactoring code, and developing APIs...
- Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, MaterialUI, Figma, Git, Azure, Jira,...

SKILL

- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript,...
- Frameworks and libraries: React, Next.js, Vue.js, jQuery,...
- UI libraries: Material UI, Ant Design, Bootstrap, Shadon/ui, Tailwind...
- State management: Redux, Redux Saga, Redux Toolkit, Zustand,...
- Databases: MySQL, SQLServer, MongoDB,...
- Development Tools: Git, Figma, npm, yarn, Jest, Webpack, GCP, Azure,...
- Agile methodology: Scrum

ACHIEVEMENTS

- React Udacity
- Google Cloud Certified Associate Cloud Engineer
- Professional Scrum Master I
- Toeic Certification from ETS